<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="113843" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Office Sales Go! [5/5 Bugfix]" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Modifies offices to actually sell their products. Fixes the office 5/5 employee bug." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
<LongDescription>
# Is Your City Experiencing a Silent Office Apocalypse?

Are you a visionary mayor, dreaming of a bustling metropolis filled with gleaming office towers and a highly educated workforce, only to be met with the perplexing reality of an economic downturn? Do you feel like your perfectly planned, pristine city is secretly plotting against you? You might be suffering from the dreaded Office Bug, a silent epidemic plaguing the urban landscapes of Cities: Skylines II!

Recognize the Symptoms!
* **Ghost Towns of Skyscrapers**: Are your magnificent office buildings, even 6x6 high-density behemoths, employing fewer people than a lemonade stand - sometimes as few as 5 in an entire skyscraper?!
* **The Unemployment Paradox**: Despite zoning endless tracts of office space, does your city boast an unemployment rate that would make an economist weep?
* **The Educated Exodus**: Are your brightest and best - those highly educated citizens you so carefully cultivated - fleeing your city faster than research grant funding after a budget cut?
* **Empty Lecture Halls**: Is your once-thriving university system now echoing with the sound of crickets and low enrollment numbers?
* **Sudden Economic Meltdown**: Did your thriving economy inexplicably flatline a few in-game years after you proudly unlocked and zoned those sleek office buildings?
* **The Unholy Trinity**: Are crime and homelessness inexplicably on the rise, even in your most affluent districts, driven by a phantom force of joblessness?
* **Shrinking Workforce**: Instead of growing, are your total employment numbers mysteriously shrinking, leaving you scratching your head at where all your citizens went?
* **The Unkillable Office**: Have you ever bulldozed an underperforming office only for it to sprout back up like a particularly stubborn weed, still employing virtually no one? And did you then resort to desperate measures, like jacking up taxes to 30% just to purge them, watching your city's finances and population bleed out in the process?
* **The Deceptive Newcomer**: Do newly built office buildings initially appear to employ a healthy number of workers, only to slowly plummet into an employment abyss, becoming yet another ghost building?
* **Perpetually Red Profitability**: Does the Profitability menu for your offices look like a perpetual bloodbath, always bathed in the ominous glow of red?
* **Stuck in the Stone Age**: Are your offices stubbornly refusing to level up, forever stuck in their basic forms, despite your best efforts?
* **The Zoning Black Hole**: Have you zoned so much office space it could cover the moon, yet your employment numbers remain stubbornly unchanged, as if swallowed by a black hole?
* **The Goods Glitch**: For the truly observant (those using Extended Tooltips), are you witnessing the baffling sight of offices with 90 000+ output goods in stock, yet no one seems to be buying them?

If you've experienced any of these terrifying symptoms, your city is in dire need of intervention! Don't let the Office Bug turn your urban paradise into an economic wasteland. Download this mod today!

# About

Modifies offices to actually sell their products.

As of 1.3, offices rarely sell their products (possibly unable to export immaterial goods). Therefore, their storages will eventually fill to their maximum (100 000) and they will be deeply in debt. This does not pose a problem in young cities where offices have empty storages, but old cities with companies that have had time to fill their storages will see a crushing lack of office jobs. Companies with full storages decrease their employee count to the minimum of 5. By forcing offices to sell their goods, they will have empty storages, which allows them to hire more employees.

**Please wait for at least 12 in-game hours with the mod on to observe an increase of employees beyond 5/5**. Companies will sell most of their stock in about 6 in-game hours and will slowly grow their workforce after that.

Possible To-Do List:
* Add a debug button that instantly increases the employee count of all offices that have a low number of workers to avoid having to wait for companies to employ hundreds of workers.
* Translation / i18n support

This is my first mod, so please tell me any and all feedback!

Notes:
* The mod will quickly force companies to sell off their stock, leaving a minimal amount to maintain production. Once their storages are empty, they will begin hiring employees. This mod does not change how quickly companies change their employee count, so office jobs will recover fairly slowly - approximately 20 jobs per in-game month per high density office. The Workplace Availability statistics will help gauge progress.
* Requires the Profit Based Industry And Office (PBIAO) mod to function, as the PBIAO mod implements most of the required functionality. This mod is tested to work on compatible versions, even if the PBIAO mod itself might not have an updated game version note, as this mod does not use all PBIAO functionality. The mod disables the modified company AI of the PBIAO mod, so there should be no effect to game files or economy simulation beyond what is said here.
* Licensed with a very corporate-friendly Boost Software License... *wink wink*

# Removal Behavior
This mod does not change your save files and can be removed at any time. However, the offices will no longer sell most of their products and the 5/5 office bug will eventually return. It is suggested to keep this mod on at all times to avoid the slow death of offices.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<!--<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Assets/OfficeSalesGo.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/workplace.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/office-sales-go-office-5-5-bug-fix.1803061/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.1" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.3.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="83825" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Beta fix for double install of the PBIAO mod." />
	<!--<ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog>-->
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/OneRandomGithubUser/Office-Sales-Go-Cities-Skylines-2-Mod" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
</Publish>
