<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="113843" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Office Sales Go! [5/5 Bugfix]" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Modifies offices to actually sell their products. Fixes the office 5/5 employee bug." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
<LongDescription>
Modifies offices to actually sell their products.

As of 1.3, offices rarely sell their products (possibly unable to export immaterial goods). Therefore, their storages will eventually fill to their maximum (100 000) and they will be deeply in debt. This does not pose a problem in young cities where offices have empty storages, but old cities with companies that have had time to fill their storages will see a crushing lack of office jobs. Companies with full storages decrease their employee count to the minimum of 5. By forcing offices to sell their goods, they will have empty storages, which allows them to hire more employees.

**Please wait for at least 12 in-game hours with the mod on to observe an increase of employees beyond 5/5**. Companies will sell most of their stock in about 6 in-game hours and will slowly grow their workforce after that.

Possible To-Do List:
* Add a debug button that instantly increases the employee count of all offices that have a low number of workers to avoid having to wait for companies to employ hundreds of workers.
* Translation / i18n support

This is my first mod, so please tell me any and all feedback!

Notes:
* The mod will quickly force companies to sell off their stock, leaving a minimal amount to maintain production. Once their storages are empty, they will begin hiring employees. This mod does not change how quickly companies change their employee count, so office jobs will recover fairly slowly - approximately 20 jobs per in-game month per high density office. The Workplace Availability statistics will help gauge progress.
* Requires the Profit Based Industry And Office (PBIAO) mod to function, as the PBIAO mod implements most of the required functionality. This mod is tested to work on compatible versions, even if the PBIAO mod itself might not have an updated game version note, as this mod does not use all PBIAO functionality. The mod disables the modified company AI of the PBIAO mod, so there should be no effect to game files or economy simulation beyond what is said here.
* Licensed with a very corporate-friendly Boost Software License... *wink wink*
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<!--<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Assets/OfficeSalesGo.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/workplace.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/office-sales-go-office-5-5-bug-fix.1803061/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.1" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.3.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="83825" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Beta fix for double install of the PBIAO mod." />
	<!--<ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog>-->
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/OneRandomGithubUser/Office-Sales-Go-Cities-Skylines-2-Mod" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
</Publish>
